她是女主角，又是我的女朋友
She is the star of the play,and she is my girlfriend.
我在跟女主角上床
I get to have sex with the star of the play!
别人都听见了 我知道
-People can hear you. -I know!
她很漂亮吧？
She looks great,doesn't she?
那个男的可真帅
That is one good-looking man.
是我眼花 还是他的腹肌真的露出来了？
Is it just me,or can you actually see his abs through his overcoat?
你做这行很久了吗？
So you been doing this long?
没有，你是第一个 把钱放在桌上
No. You're my first. Put the money on the table.
好舒服
That's nice.
不会吧
Dude!
这件上衣很贵吗？ 你说贵就贵
-ls that an expensive blouse? -lf you want it to be.
你女朋友的钮扣
Here's your girlfriend's button.
本集播出：“瑞秋的迷恋”
The One with Rachel's Crush
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
你高中的衣服裙子还在吗？
Do you still have your old blouses and dresses from high school?
应该还有几件，怎么了？
Yeah,I think I have some around here somewhere. Why?
孕妇装都好贵
Maternity clothes are so expensive.
瑞秋，那一堆是你的东西 看你要不要…
Rach,I made a pile of your stuff. If you could just...
拿皮包扔它
...throw your purses at it.
布鲁明戴尔裁了我的部门
Bloomingdale's eliminated my department.
天哪，你失业了吗？
Are you out of a job?
没有，但我被塞到专人采购部 当场矮了一大截
No,but they stuck me in Personal Shopping,which is a huge step down.
专人采购部是什么？
What is that?
陪有钱人逛，帮他们挑衣服？
Where you walk around with rich people and tell them what to buy?
听起来好棒
That sounds great!
很抱歉，我们换房子了
We switched apartments.
你不能再吃我们的 免费（意同“肉汁”）的东西没了
You can't eat our food. That gravy train has ended.
有肉汁吗？
There's gravy?
房子大就得应付人来人往
If you have the big apartment,you have to deal with people coming over.
冰箱要塞满东西 对面是你们的了
That fridge has to be stocked. That's your apartment now.
你干什么？ 我留了个甜甜圈在这里
-What are you doing? -I think I left a doughnut up here.
凯西的戏怎样？
How was Kathy's play?
凯西半裸跟一个大帅哥演床戏
Kathy gets half-naked and simulates sex with a real good-looking guy.
这就像有人把我的恶梦写成戏
It's like somebody wrote down my worst nightmare...
还要我花32块去看
...and then charged me $32 to see it.
这个点子有赚头
That's a good idea for a business.
我毁了 他们会夜夜在台上打得火热
I'm totally screwed. They're gonna be hot and heavy on stage every night...
然后去参加剧组派对 他会设法中伤我
...then they'll go to their cast parties,and he's gonna try to undermine me.
“你男朋友呢？” “他叫什么？钱斯特？”
He'll be like,"Where's your boyfriend? What's his name? Chester?"
她会说“是钱德” 他就说“随便啦”
She'll go,"It's Chandler." He'll go,"Whatever!"
这招不错
That is a good trick.
我该怎么办？
All right,look. What am I going to do?
他们是演员，那是工作
They're actors. They're there to do a job.
假戏不一定就会真做
It doesn't mean they're gonna get together.
苏珊莎兰登和提姆罗宾斯的事 不一定适用于他们
Just because it happened with Susan Sarandon and Tim Robbins doesn't mean it's gonna happen with them.
亚历鲍德温和金贝辛格
Alec Baldwin and Kim Basinger.
汤姆克鲁斯和妮可基德曼 对
Tom Cruise and Nicole Kidman.
梅尔吉普森和克林特伊斯特伍德
Mel Gibson and Clint Eastwood.
他们不是一对
They're not a couple.
喔…我听懂了
I get the game now.
他们都是演电影 舞台剧差多了
All these people were in movies together. It's much different with plays.
你们只是一起上表演课 她就跟你上床了
You were in acting class together,and she slept with you.
表演课就像舞台剧里的电影
Acting class is a lot more like a movie than a play.
我问你 他们演床戏时很火辣吗？
When they were doing it on stage,was it really hot?
是的
Oh,yeah.
那就没问题了
So you're fine.
如果两个演员私底下在一起
The rule is when two actors are actually doing it off-stage...
他们之间的火花就会消失
...then all the sexual tension between them is gone.
只要台上很火热 你就不必担心
As long as it's hot on stage,you got nothing to worry about.
热度不见了才麻烦
When the heat goes away,that's when you're in trouble.
真的？
Really?
你们看过我演的每出戏 我有擦出过火花吗？
You guys have been to every play I've been in. Have I ever had chemistry on stage?
没有 对吧
-No. -No!
你晚上要陪我去看戏吗？
Are you gonna go see the play with me tonight?
要我看你女友跟别人有多火热 我觉得很尴尬
I don't know how comfortable I am going to see how hot the sex is between them.
我知道，但是… 我人在现场
-I know,but -No,I'm there.
莫妮卡，要煎饼吗？ 你做煎饼？
-Want some pancakes? -You made pancakes?
对，拿个盘子
Grab a plate.
别过来
No,no. Stay right there.
越来越近了
Getting closer.
放心，也有谷片、松糕、松饼
Don't worry...we also have cereals,muffins,waffles and
和果酱、果肉酱和果皮酱 其实是同一种东西
...jams,jellies and marmalades,which I'm sure are the same thing.
吃吧，乔伊什么都打开了
Please eat,because Joey opened everything.
星期六要看球赛，欢迎加入 好
We're watching the game here Saturday night,if people wanna come over.
我正想找你们到对面看球 是吗？谁跟谁比？
I was thinking about having people over.Yeah? Who's playing?
球员跟球员
The players.
有人在怀念当女主人喔
Somebody seems to be missing being the hostess.
拜托！我不知道有多轻松
Please. It's a relief,is what it is,is what it is.
好，菲比，盘子准备
Pheebs,stick out your plate.
莫妮卡，我要辞职
Monica,I'm quitting.
我帮一个老女人塞上丁字裤 结果她也没买
I just helped an 81-year-old woman put on a thong,and she didn't even buy it.
我要辞职 我现在就要跟老板说
I'm quitting.I'm talking to my boss right now.
我要 我要我要我要…
Yes,I am. Yes,I am.
听到留言请回电
Okay,bye. Call me when you get this message.
沃森先生？我有事找你
Mr. Waltham? I really need to talk to you.
等一下，我忙得不可开交
In a moment,please. I'm in the middle of a task.
你有顾客上门
And you have a customer.
你好，我是约书亚
Hi.Hi,I'm Joshua.
我是瑞秋格林 有什么需要，约书亚？
I'm Rachel Greene. What could I do for you,Joshua?
我的衣服都要重买 我老婆…我的前妻…
I need a whole new wardrobe. My wife Well,my ex-wife
我真遗撼
I'm so sorry.
她把我的衣服都烧了
Anyway,she burned all of my clothes.
我救回两件，这件外套 和一条裙子
I got away with this suit and what turned out to be a skirt.
这件外套很好看
Well,at least that's a great suit.
穿裙子去干洗店可不好玩
It wasn't much fun dropping it off at the dry cleaners in the skirt.
我连内衣裤都要，如果你愿意 我整个人就交给你了
I need everything down to underwear. If you're willing,I'm all yours.
好
Okay.
瑞秋，你有事找我？
You needed to speak to me?
没有，不是我
No,no,that wasn't me.
走吧，我带你看我的内衣…
We should get started. Let me show you my underwear.
我们的内衣专柜
The selection of underwear that we carry.
对不起，是这边
I'm sorry.-It's this way.
这边？抱歉
-This way? Sorry.
对吧？他们一点感觉也没有
I'm right. Right? There was no chemistry between them.
之前的热度不见了
Before,they had heat. Now,there's no heat.
你知道这代表什么，乔伊说过
You know what this means. Joey told us what this means.
先别急着下定论 还是有一点点火花
Let's not jump to any conclusions. There was some sexual chemistry.
拜托，就像表兄妹在做爱
Come on. It was like cousins having sex.
她来了，什么都别说 冷静，别跟平常一样
Here she comes. Don't say a word. Just be cool. Don't be,you know,you.
你们好
Hey,you guys!
谢谢你们又来了
Thank you so much for coming again.
你喜欢吗？ 那当然
-Did you like it tonight? -Absolutely.
尼克点不着火柴时好好笑
Wasn't Nick funny when he couldn't get his match lit?
这是一出好戏吧？
It's a good play,isn't it?
我很喜欢 你演得很棒，尼克也是
I loved the play. You were great.And Nick,ditto.
你显然跟他有一腿
Clearly,you're having sex with him.
好…
Okay....
我显然跟他有一腿？
Clearly,I'm having sex with him?
太明显了，你们之间毫无火花
It was so obvious. There was no chemistry between you two.
让我搞清楚，你先指责我不忠 又侮辱我的演技？
You're accusing me of cheating on you,and you're insulting my performance?
这也难怪 你们每晚都光着身体爱抚热吻
I can see how this could happen. You're up there every night naked,touching,kissing.
那是演戏，这是我的工作
Acting. Chandler,this is my job.
我是在演出 你怎么可以不信任我？
I'm playing a part in a play. How can you not trust me?
我们就是这样开始的
You can understand,given how we started.
你居然拿这个来攻击我
I can't believe you're throwing that in my face.
事实如此，你刚才也没否认
That is what happened. I don't even see you denying this.
够了，等你成熟了再跟我联络
I'll tell you what,Chandler. You call me when you grow up.
那你可有得等了
Don't expect that to happen any time soon!
我的工作最棒了
I have the best job in the entire world!
来了个最帅的帅哥 我整天都在打扮他
The most adorable guy came over,and I got to dress him up all day!
瑞秋有新洋娃娃了
Rachel has a new doll!
真希望他是 我会把他跟瑞秋娃娃凑在一起
I wish he was a doll. I'd get a Rachel doll and bump them together...
让它们玩亲亲
...and make kissing noises.
他的名字最好听了 我以前都不觉得，约书亚
He's got the most beautiful name. I never realized. Joshua.
约书…亚，约书亚，约书…
Joshua.Joshua. Josh.
什么味道？
What do I smell?
不晓得，好香
I don't know. It smells good.
热腾腾的饼干，刚出炉的
Fresh cookies! Hot from the oven.
请用
Please,have some.
我随便弄了一些好吃的
I've been fiddling around here,making delicious treats for everyone.
新的“花花公子” 我随手买的
The new Playboy.Just something I picked up.
饼干和黄色书刊？好棒的妈妈
Cookies and porn? You're the best mom ever!
怎么啦？
What?
约书亚对V字领有些看法 现场听才好玩
It's just something Joshua said about V-necks,but you had to be there.
杰森穿V字领好看吗？ 是约书亚
How does Jason look in a V-neck?
随便啦
-It's Joshua. -Whatever.
等等，那不是要拿走的
Wait. Wait. This isn't takeout!
最恨吃了就走的人
-Hate to eat and run.
别走，也有女生看的黄色杂志
-No,wait. Please,don't go! I've got porn for you too.
我不需要
I don't need it.
大家应该赖在这里的
People are supposed to want to hang out here.
有什么关系？
Why? What is the big deal?
我是女主人
I'm the hostess.
不是那些臭男生 我一直都是女主人
Not those guys. I'm always the hostess.
连小的时候 别的女生都会来参加我的茶会
Even when I was little,the girls brought their dollies to my tea party.
我泡的空气最好喝
I served the best air.
那你干嘛叫大家去大的地方？
Why'd you make a big thing out of everyone hanging out in the big apartment?
我想罚他们抢走我们的公寓
'Cause they took our apartment. I wanted to punish them.
我罚完了，他们吃到苦头了
I'm done now. They've suffered enough.
要罚他们应该逼他们来这里 那倒是
If you wanted to punish them,you should have just made them hang out here.That is true.
我一定会让这里比对面好十倍
All right！This place is gonna be 10 times better than that place.
我们要捣毁对面吗？
Are we gonna trash their place?
台阶
There's steps!
贱人
Slut!
你们一定很乐于听到 凯西在跟那个人上床
You'll all be very happy to hear that Kathy is sleeping with that guy!
什么？ 你猜对了？
-What? -You were right?
我当面问她，她没有否认
I confronted her,and she didn't deny it.
我不住这里
I don't live here!
钱德 你确定吗？
Wait,are you sure?
我是醉了，但我听得懂她的话
I may be drunk,but I know what she said.
所以我跑去朱理牛排…
Then I went over to Beefsteak Chewley's....
查理牛排？ 对
-Beefsteak Charlie's? -Yes!
我们一向都很…
You and l have always been like:
真不敢相信 太糟糕了
Man,I am so sorry.
酒保教了我一个小把戏
The bartender taught me a trick,though.
我忘了
I don't remember it.
需要帮忙吗？ 不用了
-Do you need help with that? -I got it.
真惭愧，我没吸过地板
I just feel bad. I never vacuum.
我跟约书亚在一起1小时 他却没有约我
I was with Joshua for an hour today,and he has not asked me out.
真泄气 那就你约他嘛
-Just so frustrating. -Why don't you ask him out?
没错，感觉会很前卫
Totally. That's such a turn-on.
是吗？不会很饥渴吗？
Really? It doesn't seem desperate?
所以才前卫
That's the turn-on.
他刚离婚 跟女人相处可能会紧张
He just got a divorce. Right? He's probably really nervous around women.
你就先主动嘛
Maybe you just need to make the first move.
我没约过男生 你没约过男生？
-I've never asked a guy out before. -You've never asked a guy out?
没有，你有吗？ 几千次
No. Have you?Thousands of times!
这不是什么光荣的事对吧？
That doesn't make me sound too good,does it?
我连怎么开口都不会
I don't even know how I would go about it.
我会打量一个女人，然后说
What I do is,I look a woman up and down,and I say...
“你好吗？”
"Hey. How you doing?"
拜托
Oh,please!
你好吗？
Hey. How you doing?
好，我现在就打给他 约他出来
You know what? I'm gonna do that. I'm gonna call him up and ask him out.
有什么难的，约就约 你好吗？
I can do that,ask him out."How you doing?"
约书亚 我是布鲁明戴尔的瑞秋格林
Hi,Joshua. It's Rachel Greene from Bloomingdale's.
对，我想问你…问你…
I was just wondering if you...?
是不是掉了皮夹？
...left your wallet at the store today?
我们捡到一个皮夹…
We found a wallet,and we
看驾照？真是好主意
The license? That is a good idea.
我看看，驾照是一位…
Well,let's see. This license belongs to...
菲比先生的
...belongs to a Mr. Pheebs.
抱歉打扰你，明天见，再见
So sorry to bother you at home. I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
你做过几千次？ 没像你这样过
-You've done that a thousand times? -I've never done that.
我好怕他会拒绝
I just got so nervous that he'd say no.
你得让他无法拒绝，像… 尼克队的球票
You gotta give him something he can't say no to,like...Knicks tickets.
找他去看尼克队的比赛 他一定会答应
... Invite him to a Knicks game. You're guaranteed he'll say yes.
你觉得有用？ 绝对的，否则我去行吗？
-Really? You think that'll work? -Absolutely. And if not,can I go?
什么声音？
What the heck is that?
她有打来吗？
Did she call?
没有，抱歉
No. Sorry.
也许我应该打给她
Maybe I should call her.
不要，别理她了，你不必受气
Forget her,man. You don't need her.
没错，她的行为很不可原谅
He's right. What she did was unforgivable.
对，但要是我弄错了呢？
Well,yeah,but,you know,what if I was wrong?
你怎么会弄错？
How might you be wrong?
要是她没跟那个人上床呢？
What if she didn't actually sleep with the guy?
大哥，她有亲口证实吧？
Tell me she told you this.
她不必，我看了戏 他们毫无火花
She didn't have to tell me. I saw the play. There was no heat.
罗斯，说句话 你就根据这个？
-Back me up. -That's all you're basing this on?
这不是在帮我
That's not backing me up!
你说私下如果有，台上就没有
Look,you said,"With the offstage and the heat"
那只是个理论 很多理论都行不通
That was just a theory. There's a lot of theories that didn't pan out:
孤枪侠、共产主义、几何学
Lone gunman,communism,geometry.
天哪
Oh,my God!
你要不要去看篮球？
"Would you like to go to a basketball game with?"
篮球，真有意思，我正好有票…
"It's funny,basketball,because I happen to have tickets"
谁喜欢尼克队啊？
"Who likes the Knick?"
你觉得如何？
What do you think?
以一个没对象的单身女O来说
Well,as a single woman,who is available...
我觉得你很帅
...I think you look great.
没错，帅呆了
Oh,yeah. You look great.
看起来真配
This looks great.
你喜欢吗？ 很喜欢
So you like it?I do. I love it.
我决定直接穿回家
In fact,I think I'll wear it home.
太好了 谢谢你的帮忙
-Great. -Thank you so much for all your help.
那就这样
Well,I guess this is it.
谢了，春天再来找你买泳衣
Thanks.Maybe I'll see you in the spring for the bathing suits.
你不现在买吗？
You don't want to do that now?
不用了，改天见
That's okay.I'll see you around sometime.
篮球
Basketball!
什么？
Sorry?
我有两张尼克队的球票如果你有兴趣的话 好谢谢你这星期的惠顾
I have two tickets to the Knicks game if you're interested....just as a thank-you for this week.
太好了 真的？
That would be great!
对啊，太棒了 我外甥最迷尼克队了
-Really? -That would be fantastic!My nephew is crazy about the Knicks!
太棒了，谢谢你，瑞秋
This is fantastic. Thank you so much,Rachel.
早安
Good morning.
我来说声对不起
I just wanted to come over to say that I'm sorry.
我真是最白痴的白痴 我明白你为何那么生气
I acted like the biggest idiot in the world.I can completely understand why you were so upset.
我真的希望你能给我打电话的 我知道，我也很后悔
I really wish you'd called me.Yeah,I know. I wish I had too.
不过我觉得这是好事
I think this is a good thing.
我们吵了第一次架 可以进展下去了
We've had our first fight,and now we can move on.
至少我确定…
I know for me,but
尼克的裤子？ 对
Nick's pants?
看来第二次吵架会更厉害了
I think our second fight is going to be a big one!
下次要怎么说？
-For next time,what do you say?
我多一张票 是多一张票，不是两张票
-"l have an extra ticket.""An extra ticket." Not "two tickets."
你第一次约男生被拒绝了？
The first time you asked a guy out he turned you down?
他没有拒绝，他正在看球
He didn't turn me down. He's at the game.
我约到他了，只是我没去
I got the date. I'm just not on it.
都弄好了，来吧
Okay,it's ready.Come on.
什么弄好了？ 来就对了
-What's ready?Just come.
天哪
Oh,my God!
好漂亮喔
This is beautiful!
你整整忙了2天？
Did you work for two days straight?
差不多
Pretty much.
这个地板好不好？ 看起来一样
What do you think of the floor?I don't know. Looks the same.
以前是铺地毯 对喔
You used to have carpet.Oh,yeah.
我做了点心
I made snacks.
你们随便，我要稍微眯一下
Please,just hang out.I'm just gonna rest my eyes for just a little bit
要我们待会再来吗？
Do you want us to come back later?
不，留下来，继续聊天
No,no,no. Stay. Just keep talking.
我一直都是女主人
I'm always the hostess.
怎么样？
How'd it go?
她之前没跟他上床 太好了
-She wasn't sleeping with him. -Good!
现在有了
She is now.
什么意思？ 意思是她很邪恶
-What are you saying? -I'm saying that she is a devil woman.
才一转身她就跑去跟尼克上床
You think you know a person,then they turn around and sleep with Nick.
尼克和他的大胸肌，大乳头
Nick and his rock-hard pecs and his giant man-nipples.
我恨他，我也恨她
I hate him. And I hate her.
我不恨她，我爱她 都是我的错
I don't hate her. I love her. This is all my fault.
怎么会是你的错？ 因为我应该打给她的
How? How is it your fault?I should have called.
要是吵完我打给她 她就不会跟尼克约会
If I had called her,she never would have gone out with Nick.
他们就不会上床 我亲手把她送给他
They wouldn't have ended up in bed. I threw her at his man-nipples!
错不在你 就算吵架她也不该跟别人上床
This is not your fault.Your fight does not justify her sleeping with someone.
除非她以为他们分手了
Well,if she thought they were on a break....
瑞秋，你的客人掉了皮夹
Rachel,one of your customers seems to have left his billfold,
约书亚伯根 真的？
a Joshua Burgen.Really?
麻烦你通知他 好，没问题
Will you call him? -Yes,I will. Absolutely.
瑞秋 约书亚
Hello,Rachel.Hi,Joshua.
我是故意留下皮夹的 真的？
-I left my wallet here on purpose. -Really?
我想再见到你 我好高兴
Yes. I just wanted to see you again.I'm glad.
瑞秋，我有话要对你说 什么？
Rachel,I'd like to say something to you.Yes?
你好吗？
"How you doing?"